

Jose María de la Cruz Sánchez

Telecommunications Engineer Smart Contract developer

Spain

□ +34 699 19 05 83

jmariadelacruzsanchez@gmail.com

in linkedin.com/in/jmariadls/

https://github.com/jmariadlcs https://www.devscrooge.com

Stack

Smart Contract development Solidity

Frameworks and deployment

Hardhat

Javascript - Nodejs

Libraries

Ethersjs - Web3js Openzeppelin

Standard and others

ERC20 - ERC721 - ERC1155 TheGraph IPFS

Oracles and others

Chainlink Chainlink Price Feeds Chainlink VRF Chainlink Keepers

Audit

Unit testing Staging testing Slither

About me

Telecommunications engineer by University Carlos III (Madrid) and RWTH Aachen University (Germany) with a Masters Degree on Blockchain technology, Smart Contracts and Cryptoeconomy.

Due to the hours dedicated to the theoretical study of blockchain technology and my experience as a Blockchain Engineer both designing decentralized application architectures and developing Smart Contracts I am the ideal person with whom to consult - audit - develop your idea in an effective, efficient and secure way.

Education

MSc in Blockchain technology, Smart Contracts and Cryptoeconomy

2021 - Now

Universidad de Alcalá (Spain - remote)

MSc in Electrical Engineering, Information Technology, and Computer Engineering

2021 - 2022

RWTH Aachen University (Germany)

Telecommunications Engineering Bachelor's degree

Universidad Carlos III de Madrid (Spain)

Electrical Engineering and Computer Science Exchange Scholarship Awarded

2020 - 2021

2017 - 2022

University of Arkansas (EE.UU)

Cancelled due to COVID-19.

Work Experience

TortleNinja: Blockchain Engineer

August 2022 - Now

Full-time

Development of Smart Contracts, auditing an testing.

Development of API backend based on Typescript and Nodejs.

Development of frontend based on Typescript, React.

Stack used: Solidity, Hardhat, Javascript, Ethersjs, OpenZeppelin, TheGraph, Slither, IPFS, Typescript, React, Nodejs, API

Quarktium: Co-Founder, Co-Ceo and Smart Contract developer

April 2022 - Now

Full-time

Cofounded Quarktium, a science-based blockchain project. I am in charge of developing all the required smart contracts.

Stack used: Solidity, Hardhat, Javascript, Ethersjs, OpenZeppelin, ERC721, TheGraph, Slither, IPFS, Python

German

French

Languages Spanish Native English Bilingual

Basic

Basic

Smart Contract developer

March 2021 - Now

Freelance

Development of Solidity Smart Contracts, unit and staging testing and audits of the developed contracts.

Stack used: Solidity, Hardhat, Javascript, Ethersjs, OpenZeppelin, ERC721, ERC20, ERC1155, TheGraph, Chainlink, ChainlinkVRF, Chainlink PriceFeeds, Chainlink Keepers, Slither, IPFS

UST: QA Software Engineer

May 2021 - August 2021

Intership

Development of automated testing for web environments, development and testing on mobile environments, as well as research, development and implementation of new automated test environments.

Main skills: Java - XML - Cucumber - Selenium - Appium- Android Studio - AShot - Visual regressiion- Cucumber reports - Web QA - Mobile QA